export const questiondata = {
    topic: 'Javascript',
    level: 'Beginner',
    totalQuestions: 4,
    perQuestionScore: 5,
    questions: [
      {
        question:
          'Command to create NextJS app?',
        choices: ['npx new create-next-app@latest' ,'npx create-next-app@latest',
        
       ' npx new app create-next-app@latest'
        
       ,'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'npx create-next-app@latest'
      },
      {
        question:
          'Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?',
        choices: ['var', 'let', 'var and let', 'None of the above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'var and let',
      },
      {
        question:
          'on which Port NextJS app runs?',
        choices: [
          '5000',
          '3000',
          '7000',
          'None of the above',
        ],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: '3000',
      },
      {
        question: 'How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?',
        choices: ['const', 'var', 'let', 'constant'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'const',
      },
      {
        question: 'Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?',
        choices: ['Throws an error','Ignores statements','Give warning','None of above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Ignores statements',
      },
      {
        question: 'SSR stands for?',
        choices: ['Server static resources',

        'Server side response',
        
       ' Server Side Rendering',
        
        'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Server Side Rendering',
      },
      {
        question: 'When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:',
        choices: ['Boolean','Undefined','Object','integer'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Object',
      },
      {
        question: 'Access the following environment variable in Next.js??',
        choices: ['env.local.DB_HOST',

        'env.process.DB_HOST',
        
        'process.env.DB_HOST',
        
        'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'process.env.DB_HOST',
      },
      {
        question: 'Why next/link is used in NextJS?',
        choices: ['navigations to another routes',

       ' image processing',
        
       ' text formatting',
        
        'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'navigations to another routes',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following is not a Javascript framework?',
        choices: ['Node','React','Vue','Cassandra'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Cassandra',
      },
      {
        question: 'Why next/image used in NextJS??',
        choices: ['Image processing',

       ' Image Linking',
       ' Image optimization',
        
        'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Image optimization',
      },
      {
        question: 'NextJS is developed by??',
        choices: ['Facebook',

        'Google',
        
        'Vercel',
        
        'None of these'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'Vercel',
      },
      {
        question: 'What does … operator do in JS?',
        choices: ['It is used to spread iterables to individual elements','it is used to describe datatype of undefined size','No such operator exists','None of above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'It is used to spread iterables to individual elements',
      },
      {
        question: 'Command to start next.js project in development mode?',
        choices: ['npm run dev',

        'npm start build',
        
        'npm dev','None of above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'npm run dev',
      },
      {
        question: 'Which of the following are not server-side Javascript objects?',
        choices: ['Date','FileUpload','Function','All of above'],
        type: 'MCQs',
        correctAnswer: 'All of above',
      },
    ],
  }